( Watch on www.kisskh.llc )
Sir, where does boss Kenzo live?
Over there inside.
Thank you.
Oh, god!
Tsk, watch where you're going!
Sorry.
Ma’am, does boss Kenzo live here?
Over there. Inside that place.
- Thank you. - Okay.
What is it?
Um...
Where does boss Kenzo live?
Ah...
There upstairs.
The house with a blue curtain.
Thanks.
Just be careful.
A lot of people have slipped there.
Marlo?
Marlo.
Marlo!
- Kenzo. - Damn. Is that you, Marlo?
You've grown. How are you?
I’m fine, bro.
I've been waiting for you. Waiting for your call.
You just popped out of nowhere.
I was pick pocketed in the bus earlier.
What?
Just when I was about to call you.
Damn, bad luck really hit hard, huh?
Oh, Amor.
Amor!
Come here.
This is Marlo, the son of my friend that I was telling you about.
Oh yeah, the key!
Right.
- That's him? - Yes... Wait a sec.
Come, Marlo over here.
There. See?
I spent the entire day cleaning.
You're actually very lucky!
This was the only vacant room here.
It's good, right?
But bro.
This seems too big.
I'm fine with a small room.
I also don't have a lot of money.
Like maybe a thousand.
This bastard.
Then I'll just ask for a thousand.
Come on, it's you.
Would I make things difficult for you?
Your dad's the reason I got lucky here in Manila.
It's just a shame.
He passed away early.
Yeah, bro. It was so sudden.
By the way, bro.
Maybe you could introduce me to dad's job.
Because...
He left behind debts that trouble me now.
I could probably become a messenger, bro.
That's your job here, right?
Um...
But if it's hard, bro,
I've applied to online agencies.
I'm just waiting for an interview.
Oh, sure, sure. Whatever.
I'll help you, alright?
For now, rest well.
You traveled far.
I have something to do.
If you need anything, tell Amor. Okay?
- Okay, bro. - Alright.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Oh, and if you smoke, there's an ashtray.
Don't make a mess.
Got it.
Tell me if you need something.
Oh right,
I'm cooking downstairs later.
Join us.
Okay. Thank you.
Alright, Marlo, go rest.
Yes, love. I want you inside me.
Oh yeah!
- Yeah... - Yes, love.
I wanna be inside your pussy.
What?
Oh, you heard me.
Stick your phone in your cunt.
Let me do you with your phone.
You naughty-naughty, huh.
Okay, love.
A thousand tokens?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Oh yeah...
Show me what you’ve got.
Oh, so nice...
Oh, beautiful tits.
Oh, baby..
Ride it like that... Ohh...
- Just like that. - Ahh...
Oh...
Wonderful.
Hector!
Don't make me drag you out there!
Hector, face me!
Hmm?
Boss.
Damn you.
- Boss Kenzo. - You told me you'd pay on Thursday.
- You're long overdue! - Boss Kenzo.
- Huh? - You need to pay!
Boss Kenzo, promise. I'm begging you.
I'll pay you next week.
Boss Kenzo.
- You keep saying next week. - Kenzo!
- Yet there's nothing. - I promise!
- Damn you! - Next week. Promise.
Kenzo!
[murmuring]
Why so angry?
Running out of money?
[people murmuring]
Here you go.
He's already paid.
Is that okay?
Welcome home!
- Boss. - You better thank Nila for this.
Come eat.
Are you okay?
Is it about what happened with Kenzo?
I'll apologize for him.
You'll get used to it.
Amor, can I use your phone?
I haven't been able to call my family
since my phone got snatched.
Oh, but my phone's upstairs.
Later if you want.
Here.
It has unli data. Even if you use it all day.
Go on.
Amor,
let me have a taste of your feet.
I can smell it from my room. So tempting.
Here, get some.
There's a lot.
Here.
This is Amor's specialty.
Eat a lot. You won't always taste this.
Amor,
- by the way. - Hmm?
Here.
This covers next month's rent.
I'll give it to you instead of spending it on stuff.
Thanks.
How about you?
Did you pay for your room already?
Uh...
Hopefully I'll get lucky at the interview tomorrow.
So I'll be able to pay.
Uh...
Amor, I'll pay immediately.
Promise.
You look so scared.
He's new here. Still a baby.
You know.
Get used to Kenzo.
He's noisy.
But he can't kill.
Even cockroaches, right?
Nothing.
Right.
Get used to it soon.
Amor, I'll take this home, okay?
Sure. Just bring the plate back tomorrow.
You don’t eat feet?
Uh...
I do eat it.
Sometimes.
Go, eat some more.
It will make you look young.
Who are you?
You know,
you're not scary anymore.
What do you want me to do, huh?
Nothing.
Let’s just kiss.
Here you go, that’s three thousand. Huh?
Go home already.
Too cheap.
Only three thousand?
Just go home.
Amor, not now.
While your parents haven't paid yet,
you'll help Amor's business.
You should be thankful you get an opportunity here. Got it?
Okay, do well. Sell it all outside later.
So, Marlo. How was your sleep last night?
I slept well, bro.
I’m gonna leave in a minute.
There, yes. That's good.
Just don't be choosy with your job and you'll be fine.
Alright. I'll head out too.
Kenzo.
Let me see that white one.
Maybe I could go with you today.
Where?
At your job.
I'll apply, or do what's available.
So I can buy a cellphone.
You know how to drive a motorcycle?
I've tried motorcycle taxi at our place.
Wait here.
I'll come back quickly.
What now, huh?
You’re not going to pay?
You’re stubborn, huh? Give me your wallet!
You asshole!
What now? Huh?
Okay, okay!
Come on.
Come on, let’s go! Make it fast!
Faster!
Son of a bitch!
So dumb!
I thought you knew how to drive a motorcycle? Damn!
Instead of making money, I’ve spent it for the repair.
What happened?
We fell off the bike. What else?
Why did you let him drive then?
I didn’t know he’s not cool as his dad.
So, what?
Are you coming next time?
You can do side line for me.
I still need the extra helper.
That’s it.
You can do that, boy!
Apply to a restaurant and service crew as well.
You might do well there.
Maybe you're really just a rag boy.
Maybe that’s how it goes.
- Sorry. - What sorry?
Don't say that. There are no apologies here.
There’s no right and wrong with our doings.
Just don't be an idiot again. Alright?
Hello.
Hey.
Yes.
Sure. Of course. Okay.
I have a booking.
You're in charge of this kid.
What happened?
Did you know?
Kenzo and I had the same job at the start.
Perhaps
what happened to me was a blessing. I got sick.
I learned from small businesses.
It helps a lot.
It helps others as well.
So there.
I stay here while Kenzo continues his sideline.
He does a lot.
From morning until night.
I noticed.
Amor.
I saw him the other night.
What did you see?
He was heading home!
It’s almost morning.
Eat first. I bought that earlier.
That’s tasty.
Let me help you with that.
Sure. Go ahead.
Do this.
Alright.
Just like that.
Okay.
- Ouch! - Oh!
Give me that!
Your lifeline is long.
You know what they say.
When your life is long, you're a bad person.
What month were you born?
October.
Scorpio.
Horny.
There's nothing wrong with that.
As long as you use it properly.
Ah, damn!
Amor?
Are you alright?
Yes.
It's nothing. I just slipped.
Nila.
Nila, are you free?
- Nila. - I’m tired. Maybe next time.
What the hell! You’re tired?
I need money!
Drink it all up.
What's this?
I'm not a hooker.
For your load.
Go tell your mom what I did to you.
Cellphone, boss.
- What do you want, boss? That's 1500. - Sir.
- How much is it? - 1500, boss.
Just choose, boss.
Here.
Which one do you want, boss?
Anything will do.
This one, boss. It comes with load.
- How much is this? - Only 1500.
Is this good?
That’s good. It comes with load.
What’s this?
How much?
Hello? Ma.
Oh, you called. You already found a job?
Yes.
I found one.
That's great.
I thought you'd come home just to be a bum.
Ma, so...
Send the money immediately.
The debts of your dad keeps on pestering me.
Don't come home empty-handed.
Did you know?
In our province.
We had a dog before. Buknoy.
You know what's impressive about that dog?
He fought a wild pig.
Came home bloody.
Ear torn.
Broken leg.
Feeling weak.
But,
it was amusing because
he was dragging the pig
to mom's kitchen.
My family cooked it.
Ate it.
They turned it into Adobo.
Sinigang.
Lechon kawali.
It was a fiesta.
There were tons of food!
Just keep eating!
Food trip.
But you know, Buknoy.
He was under the table.
He was caressing his broken leg.
He’s still bloody.
He was weak.
Waiting for a treat.
You know what my family did?
They gave him a bone.
You know the bone that has no meat on it.
You'd think it was trash.
But you know what the hurt most?
Buknoy took the bone.
He was so happy!
His tail was wagging.
He was happy,
he was still part of the family.
Your family's wrong, boy.
They were wrong to give the dog a bone.
Boss. Boss Kenzo!
Give him a shot.
The dog
isn't given anything in return.
Hm?
A dog should be trained.
Because if you give the dog a reward, it will think...
you're all equal.
Just like with people.
Huh?
And in business too.
Never give it your all.
Because once they’re full,
they'll leave you.
Right?
They should always be hungry!
So even when trash is thrown their way.
They will still eat it.
That!
That's loyalty.
Don't ever play the hero, Marlo.
Miss, give me one beer.
Goodness, Kenzo, I'll pass.
You haven't even paid for the old one.
How selfish!
I'll pay for it tomorrow! Promise, tomorrow, I'll pay for it.
Madam.
I'll take care of what boss Kenzo wants.
There!
Here.
That's the spirit!
Keep the change.
Boss Marlon is really different.
Really different. Big time!
Just keep drinking. Just drink!
Cheers.
Boss. Let's eat, boss.
Cheers!
You. Where's your drink?
This guy drinks so slow.
- He's still drinking. - Boss, let's drink, boss.
Take a shot!
Me again?
You guys eat.
This one's nothing. He's weak.
He's down.
I thought he was strong.
Drink up.
Here, eat something.
What?
You’re running out of money again, aren't you?
Exactly.
There were lots of younger ones today.
So,
what do you need from me?
Yeah...
Hi, daddy! You want cash play tonight, right?
Put this in your mouth.
Oh!
- Shh... - Amor?
I haven't been able to watch them since you started living here.
Yeah.
Oh, baby.
Oh, so nice.
Ah, baby.
Ride it like that.
Just like that.
Wonderful.
Ah, baby.
Oh, so nice.
Just like that.
Wonderful.
Okay.
Alright.
My wife smells so good!
Okay. We're almost done!
So, can you do it? I'll leave first.
Oh! That’s early, huh?
Yeah. Just coffee.
I'll head out first.
Sure.
I used to be irresistible.
We were irresistible.
But that was in the past.
He's still giving you a bath.
He cleans me just so I won't stink.
Damn that man.
Do you know where our money comes from?
His liquor.
My medicine.
His bossy attitude.
It all came from Nila.
He's full of himself, isn't he?
But Nila is the one who keeps him alive.
To us.
When there's no hustle,
Nila.
When there's no booking,
there's Nila.
For my medicine.
For his vices. All kinds of vices.
He bought a gun he can’t even shoot.
That prostitute!
Just good at pretending to be royalty.
Is it Nila?
It’s Kenzo.
That bastard.
We're all fools.
Just fooling each other over to stay alive.
So go on,
use me.
Just
let me join as you watch.
What do you think? Do I still have charisma?
Hello?
Oh, Amor.
Shh...
Come on.
They're not here yet.
Do you want to know where our money comes from?
Get on top of her.
What?
Go on.
Who are you?
Help!
Shh...
Damn you!
This fool. It's just you.
Alright.
Stick with your plans. Perform well.
Look at that idiot.
Does your back hurt?
You've been panting since earlier.
It's just hot.
That's my job.
I'm supposed to be there.
What job?
Look at it.
All that sweat.
The creak in his bones.
Give it to him.
He sweats,
we get the money.
At least he can pay the rent.
You can rest.
Just do it with me instead.
I'll do it.
Damn. Those whores!
They mess with me of all people?
Those bastards.
Ingrates! Assholes!
Shit. Those thick faced bitches.
Huh? They're messing with me?
These bastards!
They don't know me!
Damn useless!
- Bro, wait, you're leaving? - I'm leaving!
Bro!
You think you've won?
Huh?
Do you think life's good here?
It's yours!
It's all yours!
Nila is yours.
I just don't know if you can handle that nasty personality.
Let's see if you won't die of hunger without me!
I'm leaving.
I can't do this anymore.
What?
Damn you, guys.
Kenzo!
It's okay.
Come here.
The bed is empty now.
You can move here.
What the hell?
Hey.
Where are you going?
Stay here.
You'll get worn out there.
At least here,
you'll get tired from pleasure.
Slap us.
Is this what you want?
You animals!
You animals.
Kenzo!
Animals!
Amor. Nila.
Tell him.
This is over!
- I was... - Kenzo, help.
He threatened us. He has a knife.
Kenzo!
- Huh? What are you saying? - We're so scared.
You forced me, right?
Here!
This is your money, right?
Kenzo.
It's this.
Here!
Kenzo!
You bastard!
Enough!
Kenzo, that's enough!
Marlo, stop!
Kenzo, stop!
- Kenzo, that's enough! - Kenzo, stop!
Kenzo, that's enough!
That's enough!
- Kenzo! - You piece of shit!
Kenzo!
Stop!
- Stop! - That's enough.
- Kenzo, stop! - Kenzo, stop!
That's enough.
- Stand up, you asshole! - Stop fighting!
- Stop! - Kenzo, stop, that's enough!
Are you going to kill each other?
Kenzo!
Stop!
Shit!
No.
- What did you do? - No!
Kenzo! Kenzo!
Kenzo!
You’re only mine, Amor.
You are all mine.
He’s gone.
He's also dead.